scallywagandvagabond.com 2013-12-18

# Scallywag and Vagabond | Privacy Policy » Scallywag and Vagabond

We highly value your privacy and make this policy easily available throughout our site to assist you in understanding the handling of information in the course of using this site.

**Log Files and Cookies**

This website utilizes industry standard analytics packages which gathers limited information on visitors to our website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends.

Additionally, cookies may be used to provide easier and faster access to website features such as logins and/or repeat visits. Cookies are very small text files that are stored on personal computers for reference purposes. We do/do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally indentifiable information you have submitted while on our site.

**Links to Other Websites**

This website contains links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by us. Please be aware of this when you click on any such links, we are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than our own. Consequently, we strongly suggest that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit, whether or not they are linked to by our own site.

**Registration and Use of Personal Information**

Registration is not required in order to use or access this website. However, this site may make forums, blogs, message boards or similar available to its users. You may be required to register for these features, particularly if you wish to leave comments or provide articles.

If you do register, and in the process provide us with personally identifiable information, rest assured that any such information you provide will not be shared with any third-party organization except with your express consent.

Please note that if you post comments or articles to any forum, blog or message board on this site, any personally identifiable information you provide in those comments or articles may be read, collated and used by anyone viewing them. As such, we are not responsible for personally identifiable information you may choose to make available through these channels.

**Security**

We follow accepted industry standards to protect any personal information you have provided to us. However, please be aware that no method of electronic storage can ever be 100% secure. Therefore, as is the case with any organization – we are not in a position to guarantee the absolute security of your information.

**Third Party Policies**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

**Contact Details**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please email us at christopher@scallywagandvagabond.com

$theme_options = get_option('option_tree'); $omc_google_analytics = get_option_tree('omc_google_analytics', $theme_options, false); $omc_copyright_text = get_option_tree('omc_copyright_text', $theme_options, false); $omc_enable_copyright = get_option_tree('omc_enable_copyright', $theme_options, false); $omc_enable_footer_widget = get_option_tree('omc_enable_footer_widget', $theme_options, false); $omc_footer_widget_logo = get_option_tree('omc_footer_widget_logo', $theme_options, false); $omc_footer_widget_text = get_option_tree('omc_footer_widget_text', $theme_options, false); $omc_footer_facebook = get_option_tree('omc_footer_facebook', $theme_options, false); $omc_footer_twitter = get_option_tree('omc_footer_twitter', $theme_options, false); $omc_footer_flickr = get_option_tree('omc_footer_flickr', $theme_options, false); $omc_footer_pinterest = get_option_tree('omc_footer_pinterest', $theme_options, false); $omc_footer_vimeo = get_option_tree('omc_footer_vimeo', $theme_options, false); $omc_footer_youtube = get_option_tree('omc_footer_youtube', $theme_options, false); ?>
